STEPHEN ARAMBULO

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

www.sjadev.com

stephen.jsar@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/stephenarambulo

London, N7

SKILLS

JavaScript (ES6+) React JS

Firebase Agile (scrum)

APIs Bash

Git / GitHub jQuery

TDD HTML5

Yarn / NPM CSS3 / SCSS

OTHERS

Photography Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Lightroom Salesforce

HOBBIES

Photography

Coding

Music

Sports i.e. basketball, volleyball, badminton, table tennis, bouldering

PROFILE

Experience in front-end development focusing mainly on JavaScript, SCSS and React JS framework. Completed a team-based, full client project fit as an MVP for proposal to investors. This was done with an Agile approach thus making the whole experience as close to a professional working environment as possible. Personal projects also consist of logic-based JavaScript games and responsive websites made fully with React JS and sources such as APIs and Firebase as databases.

EMPLOYMENT

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Moorgate, London

_nology || Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

An intensive 12-week training course that provides the fundamental skills and knowledge required for front-end programming. Focusing mainly on JavaScript and React JS, foundations on front-end functionality and design have been taught and utilised in producing and developing website quality. Methods on sourcing and storing data from APIs and Firebase have also been adopted as well as the use of authentication (Firebase) for user log ins. Angular, Node.js and CI/CD pipelines for deployment were also briefly touched throughout the course for better backend understanding.

Client project: "The Drop"

Produced with React JS, worked on multiple branches for different components before being merged to master for deployment and handover to product owner. Careful planning on design, component structure and merging were developed throughout the project as the Agile framework was implemented via daily scrums and sprints. Platforms such as Firebase and Spotify were also integrated to handle user data management and sourcing.

FOOD & INTERIOR PHOTOGRAPHER London, UK

Freelance || Dec 2018 - present FeaturePro || Nov 2018 - Nov 2019

Self-taught professional photographer. To view my portfolio, please visit: www.stephenara.com.

RESTAURANT PARTNERSHIPS Aldgate East, London

UberEATS || Feb 2018 - Oct 2018

Comprehensive management of key client accounts and played an integral part of the company's national expansion in the UK (UK40).

EDUCATION

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT Moorgate, London

nology || Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

A 12-week intensive course taught by _nology. Learnt the fundamental methodologies and skills required to become a Junior Software Developer.

JavaScript, OOP, React JS, Firebase and more

BUSINESS MANAGEMENT Marylebone, London

University of Westminster || Sep 2013 – Jun 2016

IT & BUSINESS STUDIES Guildford, Surrey

Guildford College || Sep 2010 - Jun 2013